hi i am anil bhis previously previously
actually there is a happy issue in my
family
but
my thanks to my company
which cover all our medical expenses but
here the insurance will not work until
uh you didn't receive the right guidance
now here i am very thankful to mr dr
anand
from
icic lombard team he helped me a lot for
finding a good hospital like gargan
garc medicals and pathways in my
city
he also helped me to settle my all
claims i was very impressed with their
service
i it's my thanks to icglambot.com
i suggest to all of you to uh
just go for it
it helps a lot
in the situations in the worst
situations if you have any medical
conditions in your family definitely it
will work for you
thanks
you